We Are Young
花样年华的我们
压制:随Feng
歌手：Fun.
Give me a second I
给我点时间
I need to get my story straight
让我理清思绪
My friends are in the bathroom
死党醉倒在洗手间
Getting higher than the Empire State
已经悄然入天
My lover she's waiting for me Just across the bar
爱人在酒吧那头等候
My seats been taken by some sunglasses
墨镜女占了我的位置
Asking 'bout a scar
谈起你我的情伤
And I know I gave it to you months ago
我知道我令你陷入情网
I know you're trying to forget
我知道你难忘伤痛
But between the drinks and subtle things
然而在酒醉金迷间
The holes in my apologies
我的道歉如此蹩脚
You know I'm trying hard to take it back
我想努力挽回你
So if by the time the bar closes
当酒吧打烊
And you feel like falling down
你的脚步蹒跚
I'll carry you home
我会带你回家
Tonight
今夜
We are young
花样年华的我们
So let's set the world on fire
将世界点燃
We can burn brighter Than the sun
令骄阳失色
Tonight
今夜
We are young
花样年华的我们
So let's set the world on fire
将世界点燃
We can burn brighter Than the sun
令骄阳失色
Now I know that I'm not All that you got
现在 我知道我已经不是你的真命天子
I guess that I I just thought maybe we could find new ways to fall apart
我猜我只是想找到更好的方式和你分手
But our friends are back
但现在我的朋友们都回来了
So let's raise a cup
那我们可以放心的畅饮了
Cause I found someone to carry me home
因为有人送我回家了
Tonight
今夜
We are young
花样年华的我们
So let's the set the world on fire
将世界点燃
We can burn brighter Than the sun
令骄阳失色
Tonight
今夜
We are young
花样年华的我们
So let's set the world on fire
将世界点燃
We can burn brighter Than the sun
令骄阳失色
Carry me home tonight
今夜带我回家
Just carry me home tonight
请今夜带我回家
Carry me home tonight
今夜带我回家
Just carry me home tonight
请今夜带我回家
The world is on my side
世界都站在我这一边
I have no reason to run
我没有理由逃脱
So will someone come and carry me home tonight
所以有人愿意今夜带我回家吗
The angels never arrived
天使并未降临
But I can hear the choir
但我听到天籁之声
So will someone come and carry me home
所以有人愿意今夜带我回家吗
Tonight
今夜
We are young
花样年华的我们
So let's set the world on fire
将世界点燃
We can burn brighter Than the sun
令骄阳失色
Tonight
今夜
We are young
花样年华的我们
So let's set the world on fire
将世界点燃
We can burn brighter Than the sun
令骄阳失色
So if by the time the bar closes
当酒吧打烊
And you feel like falling down
你的脚步蹒跚
压制:随Feng
I'll carry you home tonight
我今夜会带你回家